popsop.com 2013-06-01

# Privacy Policy – POPSOP - Brands That Teach: Advertising, Design, Branding, Digital Marketing, Sustainability

**General Statement**

Popsop (Popsop Ltd) respects the privacy rights of our users and is strongly committed to protecting their personal data online.

**Collecting and Disclosing Data**

Popsop collects personal information that you provide on this website. For example, we collect e-mail addresses when you register to receive our e-newsletters or daily news to e-mail. We use this information to communicate with you and to update you on the latest news from Popsop and our partners.

Popsop does not disclose personal information to any third parties directly, but you share your personal data with Google, Twitter and Facebook while using Popsop services, powered by these companies: FeedBurner, Tweet Feed and Popsop page on Facebook, respectively. Please refer to these companies to learn more about their Privacy Policy, if you use their services to access Popsop’s content in social media networks.

**Use of “Cookies”**

Popsop does not use “cookies” to collect your personal information.

**Third-Party Websites**

Popsop might provide links to third-party websites. Since we do not own or control those sites, we are not responsible for their privacy policy.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Popsop reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by publishing the changes on this page.

If you have any questions regarding Popsop Privacy Policy, please contact Kate Belan at **[media@popsop.com](mailto:media@popsop.com).  
**
